BRIAN M. DUMOULIN

NETSUITE APPLICATION DEVELOPER FULL STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

(M) 1-603-479-3252 / (E) bmdumoulin10@gmail.com / (L) linkedin.com/in/brian-dumoulin-10427a92

Technical Skills

- HTML5 - CSS₃ - JavaScript - AngularJS - Node.js - MongoDB - Express.js - Passport.js

- BitBucket - Git/Github - JSON - APIs

- Twitter Bootstrap - Materialize CSS - NetSuite/SuiteScript - Digital Ocean

Professional Skills

- Problem Solving - Teamwork - Communication - Fast Paced Learner

- Negotiation - Customer Service - Leadership - Management

Profile

Aspiring Full Stack JavaScript Developer with a passion for problem solving. Brings a bachelor's level education, training and experience in client and server side web development, and over 5 years of experience in management, sales, customer service, and claims. Works as an outgoing Application Developer that deals directly with clients and consultants to customize NetSuite software to better fit each business' needs. Enjoys learning new and exciting ways resolve issues using unique solutions and growing technologies.

Career History

RSM US LLP - December 2016 to Present

NetSuite Application Developer

Coding with Kids - September 2016 to December 2016

Instructor

Enterprise Holdings – January 2011 to May 2016

Claims Rep II, Claims Rep I, Management Assistant, Management Trainee

LocalEdge - January 2010 to July 2010

Multi-media Consultant

Education

RefactorU - 2016 University of New Hampshire - 2005 to 2009

Boulder, CO Durham, NH
Full Stack Web Development B.A. Sociology

MEAN Stack Minor Business Administration

Tech Projects At

WWW.BRIANMDUMOULIN.COM:8080